* English

English

​

* [\[email protected\]](https://yourdigitalrights.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Privacy Policy
==============

Last updated: February 08, 2022

Our Promise

You own your data. We exist to help you control who has access to it. We strongly believe in keeping your personal information personal, private and secure. We do not use non essential cookies and limit the Personal Data we collect from you to the absolute minimum required to deliver this Service (YourDigitalRights.org). In some cases you can turn on optional features which require you to provide additional Personal Data. Such cases require you to explicitly opt-in, and are clearly labeled. We will never sell or rent your personal information to anyone and will not retain it on our servers for more than 120 days. We will only share your personal information when it is required to provide the service or as otherwise outlined in this Policy.

Sending Requests

While sending requests (without turning on the optional request follow up feature) we ask that you to provide us with the following personal data:

* Your name
* Additional information needed to identify you with the organizations you choose to contact (such as a Username, Customer ID or Account Number)

We only use Personal Data collected when you send requests to generate an email, and do not store it on our servers.

Request Follow Ups

While using this Service, following the submission of a data request, you may opt-in to receive further support from us via email. If you choose to use this optional feature we will collect the the following additional personal data:

* Your email address
* The content of the data request emails you send to organizations and Data Protection Agencies (DPAs)
* Metadata regarding the data request emails you send to organizations and Data Protection Agencies (DPA), such as the time an email was sent and the to and from addresses

We keep Extended Personal Data for a maximum of 120 days.

By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to this website, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of YourDigitalRights.org and the authorized third parties referred to in this Policy.

Cookies and Tracking

We only use cookies to save the choices you make on the website so that it is easier for you to use the service next time. A cookie is a piece of information that the computer hosting our Service gives to your browser when you access the Service.

Data sharing and processors

We work with the following third party providers to perform some data processing tasks on our behalf. We engage these providers on terms that ensure the confidentiality and security of your data.

* Matomo: a privacy minded web analytics service by Innocraft. We use Matomo to collect anonymized information on how the Service is accessed and used ('Usage Data'). You can visit their [Privacy Policy](https://www.innocraft.com/privacy) page.
* Amazon AWS: a provider of cloud infrastructure services. When you opt-in to Request Follow Ups we use AWS to process the emails you send, store related information and send you reminder emails. You can visit their [Privacy Policy](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/?nc1=f_pr) page.

Contact

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://yourdigitalrights.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

We need your support
--------------------

YourDigitalRights.org was created because we believe that privacy matters, and that exercising your right to privacy should be easy. That's why we've made it free. By donating, or becoming a supporting member you can help ensure our long-term financial stability and independence.

[![[object Object]](/_next/static/media/powered-by-vercel.001ddbcf.svg)](https://vercel.com/?utm_source=Conscious%20Digital&utm_campaign=oss)

###### Disclaimer: This service is provided as is, without warranty of any kind. Use of this service is entirely at your own risk. We cannot take responsibility for any direct or indirect damages resulting from the use of this service. The information provided by this service along with the content on our website related to legal matters is provided for your private use and does not constitute legal advice. If you need legal advice for a specific problem, you should consult with a licensed attorney.
